之前，我们学过关于styles的内容和如何在一个独立的View中使用它们
Earlier, we learned about styles and how you can apply them
如果你想把style应用到
to an individual View. If you want to apply it to
整个activity或者应用程序
all of the views in an activity or application, you can
你可以通过在manifest文件中设置activity或者应用程序的theme属性（主题）
do it by specifying a theme attribute on the activity or
那么我们现在来修改actionbar，
application tag in the Android manifest. Now we style the action
让它更接近我们的效果图。这是settings的actionbar
bar to look like these visual mocks. This is the settings,
detail的 和 主要的activity的actionbar。对于所有这些actionbar
detail and main activity. For all cases, we want the background
我们希望它们的背景都是这个蓝色值（十六进制）
color to be this blue hex color. Then we notice that the
可以看出settings和detail的style非常相似
styling of the settings and detail activities look very similar.
它们都有app的图标和activity的标题
They both have the app icon and the activity title. On
而main activity只有logo在上面
the other hand, main activity just shows the logo. It's a
这个logo和程序图标不同，之前它通过
different attribute than the app icon, and this was provided in
asset来访问，资源名称是ic_logo。 由于这些相似点
asset drop earlier and it's called ic_logo. Because of these similarities,
我们可以在这两个activity上使用相同的theme
we can use the same theme for these two activities and
对于main activity，我们需要创建新的theme
we can create a new theme for the main activity. In
在我们的程序中，我们在这用app主题，
the case of our app, we use app theme here and
而在这我们用forecast主题。这些主题在style文件中进行修改
we use forecast theme here. We customize the themes in
style文件在values文件夹中
the styles file in the base values folder. The app
整个程序的主题继承自系统主题--DarkActionBar
theme inherits from the dark action bar system theme but
不过我们在它的基础上进行了一定的修改来符合我们的需求
we override the action bar style to be our own.
主题定义的代码在这里，我们设置了一个父类型作为它所继承的风格
This is defined here. We give it a parent ActionBar
然后把背景颜色设置成sunshine_blue
style, and then we specify the background to be the
记住这些应用会被用在settings和detail中
sunshine_blue color. Remember that this will be used in the
对于main activity,
settings activity and the detail activity. Then for the main
我们创建了一种theme叫ForecastTheme, 它继承自AppTheme, 因为这里可能需要
activity, we declare the ForecastTheme. We inherit from the AppTheme, in
添加更多属性，继承AppTheme可以让我们的修改更加自由
case there's more attributes that got added here, and then we'll be
我们在这里重写了actionbar的style。
able to inherit it for free. But we override the action bar
因为main activity显示了logo，所以我们这里需要设置logo
style to be this one. We set the logo because that's displayed
这里我们需要设置display options（显示选项）来
in the main activity, and we set the display options so
显示logo。关于actionbar的显示选项，
that we can show the logo. For more information on the action
你可以参考这个列表。为了能够向下兼容
bar display options, you can see the list here. For backward compatibility,
我们需要找到actionbar的style值
we needed to find these action bar styles in the base values
在values和value-V14文件夹中。在兼容库（support library）里对actionbar类的支持
folder as well in the values V14 folder. The action bar compact class in the
可以一直向下兼容到honeycomb
support library handles action bar behavior up
而对于ice cream sandwich以及更高版本的andorid
through honeycomb. And then for ice cream sandwich
对actionbar的支持已经包含在基础的开发框架中
and above, it goes through the framework
你可以
implementation of the action bar. You can see
从下面两个文件中找到相关代码。把这些更新加到你的程序中吧！
the code for the two files below. Go ahead and make these two changes now.